Aaron Davidge

(850)-972-8380 | aarondavidgejob@gmail.com | Mobile, AL

Summary

I'd like to describe myself as an entry-level student with the knowledge and ability of a mid-level professional. I'm currently a senior with about 20 hours shy of graduating with a BA in CS and Minor: Math. I do extensive research learning and building on my own. I've started collecting certificates to better showcase my knowledge and I'm adding personal projects daily to prove my value and ability. My skill set is very broad and I enjoy learning and working within many focuses under the areas of Computer Science, Math, Data Science and Cyber Security. I'm open to local and relocation on-premise, remote/contract and paid internships.

Education

Southeastern Louisiana University | Hammond, Louisiana BA Computer Science (Scientific) | 07/2022

(Relevant Coursework)

- *Math & Other* Calculus I, II, III, Differential Equations, Probability/Statistics with Calculus, Discrete Structures, Professional Technical Writing
- Computer Science Web Development & Design, Data Structures, Enterprise Systems, Theory of Computation, Algorithms I & II, Software Engineering, System Administration, Data Science, Operating Systems, Computer Architecture

Deans List (2018 & 2020)

Presidents List (2017 & 2019)

GPA 3.0+

Skills

Object oriented programming & design, MOB & Pair Programming, Agile, Scrum, Social Media Marketing, Video creatives, Bash scripting, Linux system programming, Test-driven development

Technical Skills

Development

- (Front-End) React.js, Javasript, NPM, Bootstrap
- (Back-End) Design, build, test and iterate REST API, SQL & NO SQL Database, PostgreSQL, PHP, Node.js
- (Mobile) Flutter, React Native

Cloud

- Azure, Google Cloud, AWS
- (Microservices) IAM, Amazon DynamoDB, S3, Lambda, EC2, Amazon Route 53, Amazon API Gateway, SNS.

DevOps

· Github, Github Pages, Github Actions, Docker, Selenium

Data Science

Python: PANDAS, NumPy, Matplotlib, Beautifulsoup,

Cyber Security

Kali Linux - Bluetooth & WPA/WP2, Social Engineering,

Programming Languages

• Python, Java, GO, C, C++, COBALT, Fortran,

Web Technologies

• HTML5, CSS3, JSON, DOM, HTTP, URL, DNS, APIs, URL

Soft Skills

· Planning, Critical Thinking, Communication, Visualization

Experience

Geaux2consulting | Hammond, Louisiana

IT Consultant/Owner | 01/2021 - Present

Provided expert evaluation of current IT needs to businesses to better facilitate future operations and satisfy technical challenges in designing and implementing a technology solution.

- · Building custom landing pages, web and mobile applications
- Designing and deploying cloud infrastructure and microservices

Uber | Baton Rouge, Louisiana

Driver | 06/2020 - Present

Transported people to appointments and destinations on schedule in a timely maner in a major metropolitan area.

- Utilized GPS devices and route tracking systems to locate optimal driving paths and avoid traffic.
- Assisted clients with vehicle entry and exit and made accommodations for handicapped individuals.

Amazon FBA | Hammond, Louisiana

Seller | 09/2019 - Present

· Scouting, purchasing, resale of retail items for arbitrage opportunity.

Certifications

- · AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Completed
- AWS Certified Solutions Architect (Associate) In Process/Dec 2022

Social

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/aaron-davidge

References

Available Upon Request